<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sample Site</title><link>http://example.org/</link><description>Recent content on Sample Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>5 key IP considerations for AI startups</title><link>http://example.org/posts/2022-10-07-5-key-ip-consideration-for-ai-startups/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/2022-10-07-5-key-ip-consideration-for-ai-startups/</guid><description>Early-stage companies are innovating new artificial intelligence-based solutions, but they often face questions as to whether such technology can be protected and the best strategy for doing so.
Without an understanding of how to protect their R&amp;amp;D investment and claim technology as proprietary, startup companies are leaving a tool behind, possibly forfeiting market share and investments as a result.
The considerations below will be useful for companies trying to understand the opportunities to protect their innovation.</description></item><item><title>Shopify agrees to consumer safety tweaks in Europe</title><link>http://example.org/posts/2022-10-07-shopify-agrees-to-consumer-safety-tweaks-in-europe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/2022-10-07-shopify-agrees-to-consumer-safety-tweaks-in-europe/</guid><description>Shopify has agreed to make changes linked to shopper safety and combating fakes after a regulatory intervention in the European Union following a number of complaints, the Commission said today.
The changes agreed to include a commitment to create a “fast and effective” ‘notice and action’ procedure for national consumer authorities to report problems they spot; and an agreement to change its templates to encourage traders to be more transparent with consumers.</description></item></channel></rss>